One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
The clouds floating in the cobalt blue,
got lost and will soak us all tomorrow.
It'll be fine if you just smile before the sunset.
If it's your wish, you can just
say a spell in your chest.
For your hopes...
Our quick premonition
is showing in the rainbow colored music notes.
Won't you come with me?
We're fallen angels,
we'll fire arrows into your dreams.
What color shall we add
into the cobalt blue?
Destroy the sad reality that reflects in your eyes.
Let's raise our wings, full of warmth.
Surreal fallen angels,
singing from our hearts.
Usopp is coming back?!
Yeah.
He was at the coast practicing.
Really?!
So, that's how it is.
Then, I'm going to get him back right away!
You really seem unaffected.
Usopp is coming back!
Wait up you guys!
I won't forgive anyone who tries to bring him back here.
Why?!
No matter what happens, it isn't you who should behave modestly, Luffy.
I won't accept him until he comes and begs.
Zoro!
Hey! Why're you being so...
What are you up to?!
Shut up!
No matter how Luffy and Usopp felt when they started to quarrel...
No matter who was right...!
After demanding a man to man duel,
You gotta devote yourself to the outcome of the battle!
And, after losing,
he left on his own accord.
Listen everyone!
Even though he's an idiot, he has the title of Captain.
The crew would be better without someone who doesn't show respect for this guy.
A crew that loses the respect for their captain, is sure to collapse.
Listen!
You can act easy going as you usually do but,
If even for an instant, the guy who is my leader let others step over him,
Next time, it is me who will leave this crew.
Eh?! That won't settle down this conversation!
If that idiot wants to come back, it's fine.
However, if he doesn't make a distinction of the current matters,
and is acting for self-interest,
then I definitely won't forgive him!
If so, it's better for you to leave Usopp on this island!
Wait up, Zoro.
It is true that he made some mistakes but,
If you just tell him what you just said when he gets back...
Is leaving the crew such an easy thing to do?!
No...
But...
Nami-san.
It is unfortunate but,
just this once, what he's saying is right.
We also can't keep trusting a guy who started such a thing on a whim.
It's simple...
If Usopp's first thing to say is a deep apology, fine.
If it isn't...
Then, there's no place for him to go back to.
What we're doing isn't a childish pirates game!
See ya, Usopp.
I've had fun until now.
You're right...
We did separate once.
There are still many days left until the ship is ready.
We'll wait for him quietly.
The Astonishing Thousand Sunny and
Usopp's Tearful Apology!
Vice-admiral Garp!
We've found the Strawhat crew's location!
They're at the southeast coast!
Currently, they're on the scrap island making arrangements to depart!
We'll go after them immediately!
Everyone get on the ship!
Yes!
Vice-Admiral Garp, this is quite embarassing after such an emotive farewell with Luffy-san and the others.
If you've any complaints, tell them to Sengoku!
He's the one who sent us here after getting angry!
He's so full of himself...
You were the one who said "Because he's my grandson" in the Den-Den Mushi after all.
You keep your mouth shut! Amateur.
A-Admiral, is it really okay for you to stay like this?
It's troublesome to go back on my bike...
Well, I'll just keep my hands off this.
I don't think that's a good idea since we're going to battle and all.
Alright! I'm going back to my friends!
The ship must be complete already.
Everyone must be waiting for me!
All what's left is to go back to the crew in the most natural way.
What, after all they're my pals.
I have 100 pattern strategies after all.
As expected this is the best one I have for my "first thing to say" speech.
Since you're all crying out and begging, I'll be glad to come back as Vice-Captain!
Thank you, Vice-Captain Usopp!
Anything you say are words that pleases me to come back!
As expected of me!
Truly a man who can raise the ones who are down!
Everyone's love for me will increase more and more after this adversity!
We'll live happily!
Alright! Hurry up!
This is a sad farewell!
Water Metropolis Water Seven!
We're off!
Brother!
The Franky Family is immortal!
Hey! Luffy!
Luffy!
Are you really sure of this, Straw Hat?
We're still waiting for one more person.
I've waited...
Ever since I heard everything about it from Sanji in that Galley-la room.
We waited for him the entire time in that place, but he didn't come.
This is the answer.
I think he also will be pleased with this.
It's not like he quit being a pirate, so we might run into him on the coming seas.
Damn it! The Navy found us already!
Grandpa?!
It's Vice-Admiral Garp's warship!
Brother! Don't look back, escape!
Hey Luffy! Can you hear me?!
Grandpa here! Grandpa here!
Answer if you can hear me!
Hey Grandpa! What's wrong with you?!
Didn't you say you weren't going to capture us here?!
Well, a lot of things happened!
I'm sorry but you're gonna die in this sea!
There's no apology I can give you but,
I'll take care of you by myself!
Hand me the cannonball.
Y-Yes.
What's he trying to do?
Fist...
Meteor!
H-He just shot a cannonball at us with his bare hands!
That flew much faster than with a normal cannon!
As if it were a baseball pitch!
My power has decreased lately.
We have no choice! We'll have to escape!
The new ship might get blown up!
Bring 1000 more cannonballs!
Yes!
This is bad!
This time many more are coming!
The Fist Meteor Shower?!
Yeah.
There's no ship that can withstand that when he uses it!
Well then, shall we begin, kiddies.
Full speed ahead!
We'll smash those cannonballs!
Got it!
Damn it! Is he really not coming?!
What is he doing?
He's here!
Usopp came!
Hey, everyone! Usopp came!
Really?
Yeah!
Move! Move!
Please move!
Move a little please!
Hey, Nose-Bro!
What're you doing here?!
What's going on?!
The marines haven't come, so why's the ship leaving?!
I was pretty sure you were on it!
What're you guys doing?!
The great me is still here!
Why?
Why?!
Even after the quarrel I was fighting alongside you all the time!
There's no way you have forgotten...
That the king of snipers under all those activities, Sogeking, is me!
Did you forget about me just because I changed my appearance?!
Wait!
Hey! The stairs are broken, be careful!
What's wrong? Hey!
Hey guys! Be at ease, I'm coming back right away!
You idiots!
Stop already!
Rubber...
Balloon!
Usopp came, Luffy!
Usopp is here!
Protect the ship!
Hey! Be happy, it's me!
Chopper, we're having nice weather today.
Let's go fishing!
I guess that's out of the question.
By the way, I have some good news!
When I get back I'm willing to take the position of Vice-Captain!
How is that? Hey!
Hey! Luffy! Everyone!
I understand!
You're so happy that you can't stop crying, right?!
That's it, right?!
Luffy.
I must not stay with you,
I brought you nothing but trouble after all.
You guys, don't tell me you actually believed that joke back then?!
We've known each other for a long time now.
There's no way I can be serious about such a thing!
We argued quite a lot, but we're still friends!
Let's leave the past behind!
Hey! Say something!
Stop messing around everyone!
Luffy, Usopp is calling for us!
I don't hear him.
Zoro!
I can't hear anything!
Liar! You can hear him!
Stop joking.
What's going on...
Do you really mean to leave without me?
I see... good enough.
If that's how you want it,
I have only one more thing to tell you...
Wherever I'm headed from now on...
is none of your business.
I'm leaving this crew!
I'm sorry!
I'm sorry for my stubbornness!
I was wrong!
Usopp!
Even though I was stubborn until now...!
Even though I said I was leaving the crew...!
I want to change all that, but I can't!
I can't, so I beg of you!
Please take me back with you guys!
Just one more time...!
Let me be your crewmate!
Luffy...
You idiot!
Hurry up and grab on!
You're the idiot!
You two guys are pitiful.
We are finally complete!
Let's hurry up and get outta this bombardment to go for more adventures, men!
Do your best, town heroes!
They'll be crushed before they can get away!
Hey! You shouldn't be cheering them on!
Don't give up! Straw Hats!
Run! Run! Run!
Brother!
What the...?
W-What's going on?!
They're furling the sails?
Have they given up?
Given up?
It's not that, but...
What're you up to, Luffy?
Hurry up! Furl the sails!
Hey! Are you really sure about this, Franky?
Idiot! You gotta trust this ship!
That's right! You gotta trust, idiot!
Idiot! Moron!
Usopp, just a while ago you were...
Well... it's okay...
Help out, you guys!
A name?!
At a time like this?!
That's right, a ship without a name won't be any good at sailing.
Well, it's gotta be Lion-like.
Alright!
I just thought of an awesome name for it!
The Bear!
The Polar Bear Lion!
That's such a weird name for a ship!
Then, The Tiger Wolf Lion!
Stop that animal enumeration!
It's like some sort of curse!
Squid! Octopus! Chimpanzee!
Without Lion on it?!
Well, Lion is good for a ship.
Even though, the guys from Galley-La didn't get it.
This big head should do fine.
Yeah, it's a nice sunflower!
That's not it, idiots!
Well, I don't blame you for your mistake...
But, this is the ship the future Pirate King will ride.
That's what you were hoping for, right Franky?
That's right.
One appropriate for sailing the seas like a wild beast and reaching the summit!
A wonderful sun indeed.
That's not it, idiot!
A strong ship as bright as the sun that can cheerfully overcome 1000 seas...
Something fit for those words.
I told you no, Idiot-burg!
How does this name for the ship sound, Franky?
The Pirate Ship...
Thousand Sunny!
That's so cool!
That's much better than the Dango Gorilla Lion name I just thought of!
Are you playing Scrabble?!
That's even better than the Lionel Master name I thought of.
Better than my Being of Darkness...
And my Monsieur Sunflower.
Have you all lost your minds?!
A ship that can sail a thousand seas sounds nice...
So does the sunny part.
Wait up you guys!
This is only the beginning.
The certain name for it is one I prepared!
Listen!
This ship's name will be...!
Let's go with the Old Man Iceburg name, I like it!
The New Battle Franky Lion Gang Champion!
Thousand Sunny, is a good name.
Lion Gang Champion!
Agreed!
It's a pleasure, Sunny!
Now that the name is decided, our trip is finally underway.
You're right.
Hey, Franky!
What're you complaining about over there?!
Hurry up and shake off this so called secret weapon!
Yeah, make haste!
The warship has almost caught up with us!
I know! Shut up!
Take one last look at this beautiful Water Metropolis.
In moments, you won't even be able to see this island's shadow!
I see.
Grandpa!
Also, Coby and...!
I'm glad I had the chance to see you after a long time!
Say my name!
What are you talking about, Luffy?!
There're still many cannonballs left!
Fist...
Meteor!
It's no use!
From now own, we'll be serious about escaping!
Let's meet again someday!
Luffy-san is so cool!
Bastard!
You're the son of my son and yet you dare understimate me, Luffy!
V-Vice-admiral Garp, please calm down!
Old Man Ice!
We got the name for the ship!
Thanks for such a great name!
Everyone! Thanks for everything!
We're going now!
Sounds like he's saying something!
I can't hear him.
It seems those who are pirates can't set off quietly.
Well, here we go!
The giant air cannon strengthened with the treasure wood Adam!
The Miracle Emergency Acceleration Device!
If you dare underestimate me...!
R-Run! Luffy-san!
You'll get killed!
Franky, hurry up!
You'll get hurt!
We're dead!
Coup de...
French: Shot
Burst!
The ship...!
Got away flying!
They made it...
Awesome!
I remember this sensation!
Merry.
It uses three barrels of cola, but it can send us flying 1 km away.
There's not a single thing the Going Merry you were riding could do that this ship can't!
It's better in many ways!
However, that ship's brave soul lives in The Thousand Sunny!
If it gets damaged, I'll fix it up as good as new!
Anything related to the ship's maintenance and weapons, you can leave them to me!
Starting today, this is your ship!
Geez...
They got away...
As expected from my grandson.
He decided not to come with us after all.
It seems so.
However, the King of Snipers promised that everyone will visit Elbaf someday.
I'm looking forward to it.
We can wait patiently; a Giant's lifespan is 300 years after all.
That was some work!
Indeed.
Well, time to go back to headquarters.
We're definitely coming too!
There's still much work to be done!
Let's go back to the station.
Chimney, Gonbe.
Well then...
What would Brother do?
No idea.
We just did as Brother said.
We'll starve to death.
Iceburg!
I thought this would happen...
W-What do you want?!
Why did you come here?!
If you're looking for a job, I can give you one.
Send one guy per day to the Galley-La office.
A-Are you sure, Ice...?!
No!
Brother!
New Brother!
Stop that.
In the Grand Line on an Island somewhere
Commodore Smoker!
Good work!
You say this pirate was worth 50 million?
Too easy...
What's happening to the army standards?
Geez...
Day after day is the same...
Smoker-san!
Ensign Tashigi!
Have you seen the wanted posters?!
The Straw Hats...
Who are you talking to?
I-I'm sorry.
Wear your glasses, idiot!
The Grand Line
Sand Kingdom Alabasta
W-What...?!
Nico Robin?!
What is Miss All Sunday doing in Luffy-kun's crew?!
She's indeed one mysterious woman but...
If this reaches Vivi-sama's ears, she'll be really sad.
Oh? That? I knew, but...
It's no big deal.
No big deal?!
We thought you'd be the most shocked about this!
You won't understand what Luffy-san is thinking even if you were very close to him.
It's no use thinking about it.
However, I can believe in everything they do.
He's the man who's gonna be the Pirate King.
He's on a different scale than us.
What tolerance!
You sure have grown up, Vivi-sama!
Hey, why're you crying?
A marine is a marine...
As long as the Navy is an organization, there's a limit to doing what I want.
The most essential thing now is rank.
After the events at Enies Lobby, all the pirates in the world will start ceding the way to the Straw Hats.
Yes.
I swear upon my pride...
I'll definitely crush them in the New World!
Everybody!
Ready?!
Yeah!
Then, for the return of Robin and Usopp,
And for our new crewmates, Franky and...
The pirate ship Thousand Sunny!
Cheers!
Let's go! Our next step is Fish-man Island!
Translation, Cornman @ Vegapunk Fansubs
Initial timing, Hedi @ Vegapunk Fansubs
Timing, Galaxy 9000
Quality checking, Sewil
Editing, Sewil
Soundtracking, MaideV and Halee
Raw providing, SOFCJ-Raws